<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 days meditation</string>
    <string name="subtitle">Every day advice - the way to inner peace</string>

    <string name="day_label">Day %d</string>

    <string name="tip_1_title">The Beginning</string>
    <string name="tip_2_title">4-7-8 Breathing</string>
    <string name="tip_3_title">Body Scan</string>
    <string name="tip_4_title">Mindful Eating</string>
    <string name="tip_5_title">Mindful Walk</string>
    <string name="tip_6_title">Loving-Kindness Meditation</string>
    <string name="tip_7_title">Observing Thoughts</string>
    <string name="tip_8_title">Box Breathing</string>
    <string name="tip_9_title">Morning Silence</string>
    <string name="tip_10_title">Anchoring in the Present</string>
    <string name="tip_11_title">Safe Place Visualization</string>
    <string name="tip_12_title">Candle Meditation</string>
    <string name="tip_13_title">Counting Breaths</string>
    <string name="tip_14_title">Mindful Listening</string>
    <string name="tip_15_title">Halfway Point</string>
    <string name="tip_16_title">Belly Breathing</string>
    <string name="tip_17_title">Gratitude Meditation</string>
    <string name="tip_18_title">Mindful Movement</string>
    <string name="tip_19_title">Space Between Thoughts</string>
    <string name="tip_20_title">Sound Meditation</string>
    <string name="tip_21_title">Evening Unwinding</string>
    <string name="tip_22_title">Forgiveness Meditation</string>
    <string name="tip_23_title">Sky Gazing</string>
    <string name="tip_24_title">Mantra Meditation</string>
    <string name="tip_25_title">Digital Detox Hour</string>
    <string name="tip_26_title">Alternate Nostril Breathing</string>
    <string name="tip_27_title">Sunset Meditation</string>
    <string name="tip_28_title">Accepting Impermanence</string>
    <string name="tip_29_title">Open Presence Meditation</string>
    <string name="tip_30_title">30 Days Completed!</string>

    <string name="tip_1_short">5 minutes of simple breath observation</string>
    <string name="tip_2_short">Calming 4-7-8 breathing technique</string>
    <string name="tip_3_short">Mindful body scan from head to toe</string>
    <string name="tip_4_short">Eat slowly and mindfully without distractions</string>
    <string name="tip_5_short">10-minute mindful walking practice</string>
    <string name="tip_6_short">Wishing happiness to yourself and others</string>
    <string name="tip_7_short">Watch thoughts pass like clouds in the sky</string>
    <string name="tip_8_short">Military-grade stress relief breathing</string>
    <string name="tip_9_short">Start your day without information noise</string>
    <string name="tip_10_short">5-4-3 grounding technique for presence</string>
    <string name="tip_11_short">Visualize your peaceful safe place</string>
    <string name="tip_12_short">Focus on candle flame for 5 minutes</string>
    <string name="tip_13_short">Count your breaths from 1 to 10</string>
    <string name="tip_14_short">Listen to music with full attention</string>
    <string name="tip_15_short">Celebrate 15 days and reflect on changes</string>
    <string name="tip_16_short">Diaphragmatic breathing for relaxation</string>
    <string name="tip_17_short">Feel genuine gratitude for 3 things</string>
    <string name="tip_18_short">Slow shoulder movements as meditation</string>
    <string name="tip_19_short">Find peace in the gap between thoughts</string>
    <string name="tip_20_short">Listen to all sounds without judgment</string>
    <string name="tip_21_short">Release the day\'s events before sleep</string>
    <string name="tip_22_short">Practice self-forgiveness and compassion</string>
    <string name="tip_23_short">Watch clouds for 10 minutes</string>
    <string name="tip_24_short">Repeat a calming word or phrase</string>
    <string name="tip_25_short">One hour completely screen-free</string>
    <string name="tip_26_short">Balance brain hemispheres with nostril breathing</string>
    <string name="tip_27_short">Mindfully watch the sunset colors</string>
    <string name="tip_28_short">Embrace life\'s temporary nature</string>
    <string name="tip_29_short">Allow everything to exist in awareness</string>
    <string name="tip_30_short">Foundation for lifelong meditation practice</string>

    <string name="tip_1_description">Find a quiet place, sit comfortably, and simply observe your breath for 5 minutes. Don\'t try to change anything — just observe.</string>
    <string name="tip_2_description">Inhale for 4 counts, hold your breath for 7, exhale for 8. Repeat 4 times. This instantly calms the nervous system.</string>
    <string name="tip_3_description">Lie down and mentally scan from your heels to the crown of your head, noticing sensations in each part of the body without judgment or evaluation.</string>
    <string name="tip_4_description">During one meal, put away your phone. Eat slowly, noticing the taste, texture, and aroma of each bite.</string>
    <string name="tip_5_description">Take a 10-minute walk. With each step, notice how your foot touches the ground. Listen to the sounds around you.</string>
    <string name="tip_6_description">Close your eyes and mentally wish yourself happiness and health. Then wish the same for loved ones, strangers, and all beings.</string>
    <string name="tip_7_description">Imagine your thoughts are clouds in the sky. You are the sky itself. Watch thoughts come and go without clinging to them.</string>
    <string name="tip_8_description">Inhale for 4 counts → hold for 4 → exhale for 4 → hold for 4. This rhythm is used by the military for stress relief.</string>
    <string name="tip_9_description">Before picking up your phone in the morning, sit in silence for 3 minutes. Simply feel what it\'s like to start the day without information noise.</string>
    <string name="tip_10_description">Name 5 things you see, 4 you hear, 3 you can touch. This instantly brings you back to the here and now.</string>
    <string name="tip_11_description">Close your eyes and imagine a place where you feel completely at peace. Examine every detail, feel the warmth and safety.</string>
    <string name="tip_12_description">Light a candle and watch the flame for 5 minutes. When your mind wanders, gently return your attention to the fire.</string>
    <string name="tip_13_description">Count each exhale from 1 to 10, then start again from 1. If you lose count, don\'t worry — just start over. This is the practice.</string>
    <string name="tip_14_description">Play your favorite music and listen to it completely, without doing anything else. Follow each instrument individually.</string>
    <string name="tip_15_description">Congratulate yourself on 15 days of practice! Write in your journal: what has changed in your state during these two weeks?</string>
    <string name="tip_16_description">Place your hand on your belly. Breathe so that your hand rises on the inhale and falls on the exhale. This activates the parasympathetic system.</string>
    <string name="tip_17_description">Recall 3 things you are grateful for today. Don\'t just list them — truly feel this gratitude.</string>
    <string name="tip_18_description">Perform 5 slow circular movements with your shoulders, fully focusing on the sensations. Simple movement can be meditation.</string>
    <string name="tip_19_description">When you notice a gap between two thoughts — pause in it. This is the silence of your true self. It is always there.</string>
    <string name="tip_20_description">Close your eyes and simply listen to all the sounds around you without categorizing them. Let sounds come and go like waves.</string>
    <string name="tip_21_description">Before sleep, lie down for 5 minutes and mentally \"release\" each event of the day. Imagine tension flowing out through your toes.</string>
    <string name="tip_22_description">Think about a situation that worries you. Say to yourself: \"I forgive myself. I did the best I could at that moment.\"</string>
    <string name="tip_23_description">Lie on the grass or simply look out the window at the sky. Watch the clouds for 10 minutes without thinking about anything specific.</string>
    <string name="tip_24_description">Choose a word or phrase (like \"peace\" or \"all is well\"). Repeat it quietly for 10 minutes, returning to it each time your mind wanders.</string>
    <string name="tip_25_description">Spend one hour completely without screens. Notice what you feel: discomfort is a signal of dependency.</string>
    <string name="tip_26_description">Close your right nostril, inhale through the left. Close the left, exhale through the right. This exercise balances the two brain hemispheres.</string>
    <string name="tip_27_description">If possible, watch the sunset mindfully. Don\'t take photos — just watch how the colors change. This will never happen again.</string>
    <string name="tip_28_description">Sit and reflect: everything good and bad in life is temporary. Feel how this frees you from clinging and resisting.</string>
    <string name="tip_29_description">Don\'t focus on anything specific. Simply allow everything — sounds, thoughts, sensations — to exist in the field of your awareness.</string>
    <string name="tip_30_description">You have created the foundation for a lifelong practice. Meditation is not a destination, but a way of traveling. Continue every day.</string>
</resources>